Hi-Rez Studios® Privacy Policy

Effective as of April 20, 2021.

Hi-Rez Studios, Inc. (“Hi-Rez,” the “Company,” “we,” or “us”) respects the privacy of its users

and recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We are

committed to safeguarding and handling your Personal Information in a responsible and secure

manner.

We have adopted a companywide Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) that guides how we process your

Personal Information in connection with your access or use of the Site (as defined below) or any

Hi-Rez game(s) or subscription service(s) offered through the Site (the “Service”). When we

collect, access, use, or do anything with your Personal Information on our website or through our

Services, we are “processing” your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy also applies to

information or data that may be collected by Hi-Rez offline as described in this Privacy Policy

below. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of any videogame developed and/or published by

Hi-Rez, and the following websites operated by Hi-Rez and any such other websites established

by Hi-Rez or its subsidiaries from time to time which reference this Privacy Policy, including

without limitation (collectively, the “Site”).

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of Hi-Rez’s Terms of Service and Use

Agreement.

In addition, Hi-Rez owns several other domain names that link or point to the websites listed above,

and we will from time to time add new games and new websites that may or may not be listed

above. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to the websites maintained by Hi-Rez, and

not to websites maintained by third parties to which the websites listed above may link.

By using the Site or any of our Services, you signify your consent to this Policy. If you do not

agree to this Policy, please do not use the site or any other Hi-Rez Services. Note that this

Policy may change from time to time, so please check back regularly to stay informed of any

changes. Material Changes to this Policy may be posted on the site. Your continued use of

the Site of the Service, or accessing your Account, following any such changes, constitutes

acceptance of such changes.

Table of Contents

1. Information We Collect Through Your Use of the Services

2. How We Use Your Information

3. How We Share Your Information

4. Your Choices

5. Third Party WebSites

6. Children’s Privacy

7. Transfer of Your Personal Information

8. Retention

9. Safeguarding Your Personal Information

10. Notice to California Residents

11. Notice to Residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland

12. Communications

1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES

“Personal Information” includes any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is capable of

being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular

individual. We may collect several different types of Personal Information when you are accessing

or using our Services, including.

(a) Information You Provide to Us.

Personal Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include, but is not

limited to, your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, birth date, created username

and password, age, and gender. Such Personal information may be collected through:

• Account Information: Information you provide about yourself to use our software or

online services (including, without limitation, when you register for an account with Hi-

Rez), so that we may communicate with you and provide you with the Service;

• Self-Reported Information: Information you provide about yourself, as well as records

and copies of such correspondence, when you purchase goods or services through the Site

or Service, register for warranties, register for games or special game-specific event

participation, or further contact us.

• Voluntary Information: Information you provide to us voluntarily by filing out marketing

surveys, email campaigns, participating in message boards, newsletters, and contests, or

subscribing to other offerings on the Site. We may also ask you for Personal Information

if you report a problem with the Site or Service. We do not require this information to gain

access to the Site; however, you may not use certain features, products, or services

(including, without limitation, the Service) that require registration, or receive materials

(e.g., newsletters), unless such information is provided.

Additionally, your participation in tournaments or other online game events is conditional

upon your agreement to us collecting, using, storing, transmitting, and publicly displaying

performance and statistical data (e.g., your scores, rankings, and achievements) generated

through your participation in the foregoing. Prize winners may also be required to provide

Social Security or Social Identification Numbers for tax purposes.

• User Contributions: You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online

message boards, chat rooms, forums, or in creating user “profiles” when you play games

on our Site or utilizing the Service. User Contributions that you disclose in message boards,

chat rooms, forums, or in “profile” information is public information, and there is no

expectation of privacy or confidentiality. We cannot control the actions of other user or

third parties with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Please see our

Terms of Service and Use Agreement on this point and for other guidelines about posting

content on our websites.

(b) Usage Information Automatically Collected.

When you play our games, visit our Site, or use our Services, we automatically collect information

about the Services you use and how you use them (“Usage Information”), as described below:

• Service Data: When you play our games, we may retrieve information about your

hardware system, gameplay and how our games are used, including, without limitation,

your Internet Protocol Address, your gameplay characteristics and patterns, information

about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, information about online

activity (e.g., feature usage), gameplay statistics and scores, user rankings, and click paths

and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We use this information

to enable you to play our game(s) over the Internet. We may also combine such information

with other demographic information to better understand the behavior and preferences of

our customers so that we can improve our Services and for marketing and advertising

purposes.

• Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies: We may use various tracking technologies

to collect and store information about your use of our Services. We use these tools to ensure

that you receive a personalized experience, to provide you with certain functions on our

Services, to keep your account safe, and to improve and optimize our Services, and to

inform our marketing efforts. Please refer to our Hi-Rez Studios Cookie Policy for more

information, available at <https://www.hirezstudios.com/legal/\>.

(c) Information We Receive from Third Parties

We may receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, business

partners, our affiliates, or publicly available sources. Further, if you log into your user account

through social media sign-in services (e.g., Facebook Connect), you provide Hi-Rez with

permission to collect, store, and use any and all information in the same manner and to the same

extent that you agreed the social network or third party platform could collect, store, or use the

information. Once the Personal Information has been transferred to the Site from a third party, you

may or may not be able to rescind or remove the information.

We obtain contact details and other Personal Information regarding media contacts and social

media influencers from a variety of sources including Cision. If you wish to know more about how

such information is collected and used, please refer to Cision’s privacy notice at

<www.cision.com/us/legal/privacy-policy\>.

2. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Your Personal Information may be used for various purposes, including:

(a) To Communicate with You

The Personal Information you provide will allow us to alert you to new products, features,

enhancements, special offers, upgrade opportunities, contests, and events of interest. While we may

send emails that may contain information regarding third party products or services, this does not

mean that we have provided or traded your Personal Information to any party. Additionally, we

may use survey information in our voluntary marketing surveys to select and direct advertising

that is more likely to be of interest to a particular user of an account with Hi-Rez. This information

may be transmitted to an ad server owned by an advertising company to match account holders

with ads that they are more likely to be interested in. You can manage your email preferences and

opt out of certain communications. However, Service-related communications, as well as security

and legal notices, are necessary for us to continue to provide our Services to you.

(b) Marketing and Advertising

We may process your Personal Information in order to create, deliver, monitor, and/or assess the

success of our advertising and marketing efforts. We may show you interest-based advertisements

or send you marketing communications based on information we’ve collected about you. Please

see Section 4: Your Choices below for more information about how to opt-out of certain marketing

communications.

(c) For Research and Development

We may share aggregate consumer data (which does not contain Personal Information) with the

advertising companies or with any other third party, and we may use such information for any

legitimate business purpose in our sole discretion. Additionally, we may utilize your Personal

Information for internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our

websites to better meet our visitors’ and users’ needs.

(d) To Enforce our Terms, Agreements, or Policies.

To maintain a safe, secure, and trusted environment for you when you use the Services, we use

your Personal Information to make sure our terms, policies, and agreements with you and any third

parties are enforced. We actively monitor, investigate, prevent, and mitigate any suspected or

actual prohibited activities on our Services. We are required to process your Personal Information

for this purpose to provide our Services.

(e) To Comply with Applicable Laws.

We may be required to process your Personal Information under certain laws and regulations, such

as tax laws. We will also process any and all information to law enforcement agencies or others if

required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably

necessary to: (a) comply with legal or regulatory process (such as a judicial proceeding, court

order, or government inquiry) or obligations that we may owe pursuant to ethical and other

professional rules, laws, and regulations; (b) enforce the Company’s Terms of Service and other

policies; (c) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third parties; or (d) protect the

rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its employees, its users, its clients, and the

public. We cannot provide the Services to you without such processing.

3. HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this Policy, we disclose Personal

Information in the following situations:

• Affiliates and Acquisitions. We may share your Personal Information with our corporate

affiliates (e.g., parent company, sister companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other

companies under common control). In the event of a merger, acquisition, asset sale, or in

the unlikely event of bankruptcy, visitor and user information (including, without

limitation, Personal Information) maintained by Hi-Rez may be transferred to its

successors or assigns.

• Service Providers. We may share your Personal Information with service providers we

use in connection with the Service. Among other things service providers may help us to

administer our website, conduct surveys, provide technical support, assist in the fulfillment

of orders, aid in auditing practices, process payments on the Site, and for other legitimate

purposes permitted by applicable law. Such service providers may have access to your

Personal Information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are

obligated not to disclose nor use such information for other purposes.

• Google Analytics Hi-Rez uses the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting

features of Google Analytics for Display Advertising. You may opt-out of Google

Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads by visiting

the Google Ads Preference Manager, which is available at

<https:\www.google.com\settings\ads\>

Google Analytics is an analytics service provider. Learn more about how Google collects

and uses data at <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites\>. To opt out of

Google Analytics Advertising Features please use Google Ad Settings at

<https://adssettings.google.com/\>. To opt out of Google Analytics entirely please use

<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout\>.

• Other Disclosures with Your Consent. We may ask if you would like us to share your

Personal Information with other unaffiliated third parties who are not described elsewhere

in this Policy.

• Other Disclosures without Your Consent. We may disclose Personal Information in

response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, in connection with any legal process, or

to comply with relevant laws. We may also share your Personal Information in order to

establish or exercise our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or

take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or

property, or a violation of our policies, or for any other proper purpose to law enforcement,

or the appropriate judicial or civil authorities.

• Partner Promotion. Users who register for an account with Hi-Rez may register for other

third party partners from our Site, or link a Hi-Rez account to an account with such third

party partners, from time to time. If you opt-in to any of these services, we may collect

additional information including, without limitation, information requested by a third

party, and pass this information, together with all other Personal Information, to that third

party partner. Use of your Personal Information by a third party partner will be governed by

that third party provider’s privacy policy and terms of service. We may also retain any

additional information collected for use in accordance with the terms of this Policy.

Participation in these other related services is optional and is not required to access our

Site, though some functionality may depend upon it.

4. YOUR CHOICES

For Personal Information that you have provided or that we have collected, you have the following

choices:

(a) Your Account Information

You may edit some of your Personal Information through your account or ask us to change, update,

or fix your Personal Information in certain cases, including if it’s inaccurate. When you update

your account information, we may keep a copy of your previous account details for our records

and to prevent fraud or other activities that violate our terms, policies, and agreements.

Additionally, please note that by removing some of your data, your ability to use certain

functionality of the Website may be limited. Further, if you do not provide us with certain Personal

Information, we will no longer be able to provide you with access to certain Services.

(b) Communication Preferences.

When you register your account, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of receiving

Hi-Rez marketing communications, including event invitations, special offers, and newsletters. If

you choose to have your account removed from our mailing list, you can do so by adjusting your

communications preferences or click the unsubscribe link within the email you received from us.

You will not be able to unsubscribe from Service-related communications as they are necessary

for us to continue offering you the Services.

To make these or any other requests with respect to your Personal Information, you may contact

our support desk at <http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/\> or email

PrivacyRequests@hirezstudios.com. We ask that you describe, in reasonable detail, identify

yourself and identify the information requested to be accessed, corrected, or removed. We will

then review, update, or remove information as appropriate within a commercially reasonable time

frame after receiving such notice from you. You can also change your settings for receiving

marketing communications on your Hi-Rez Account page at any time. We may decline to process

requests if we cannot verify the requestor’s identity, if we believe the change would violate any

law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect, or for a similar purpose. In any

case, where we provide information access, deletion, or correction, we perform this service free of

charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

5. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

You may find links to third party websites, payment applications, and widgets on our Site or

Services, that we do not own nor control. When you interact with such links or applications, you

may leave the Hi-Rez Site you are visiting and go to the website you selected. For example, you

may be required to establish a STEAM account with Valve Corporation to use our game(s), and you

may be required to provide credit card and other information to Valve Corporation and our other

third party payment processors when you purchase products or services from our Site or through

our Service. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to

read their privacy statements. Once you leave our Service or are redirected to a third-party website

or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our Site’s Terms of Service.

The Site may also offer you the ability to share your Personal Information through a social

networking site (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn), using such social networking site’s integrated

tools (e.g., Facebook “Like” button, or Twitter “Tweet” button). The use of such integrated tools

enables you to share Personal Information about yourself with other individuals or the public,

depending on the settings that you have established with such social networking site. Additionally,

by making Personal Information available on the Site, you “opt in” to allow Hi-Rez to provide

such Personal Information to a social networking site without your further consent. For more

information about the purpose and scope of data collection and use in connection with such social

networking site or a site’s integrated tools, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that

provide these social networking sites.

6. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Hi-Rez does not permit access to the Site or Services by children under the age of 13. If you are

under 13 years of age, you should not access, or attempt to obtain access to, the Site or Services.

The Site does not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is under the age

of 13. If your child is under 13 and you believe they are accessing the Site and Services, please

contact us at PrivacyRequests@hirezstudios.com. Teenagers age thirteen or older, but who are

under the age of eighteen must have their parents or guardians review this Policy and should

encourage them to contact us if they would like to raise any concerns. For more information, we

encourage you to review our Parent Information page, available at

<http://www.hirezstudios.com/parents\>.

7. TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Hi-Rez maintains and stores your Personal Information on servers located within the United States.

This may not apply to Hi-Rez’s third party providers (including, without limitation, Valve

Corporation and our third party payment processors). In the event that Hi-Rez becomes a global

organization, some of the computer systems on which Hi-Rez collects, stores, and uses the

information it collects or receives may be based outside the United States. Therefore, your Personal

Information may be transferred to, used, processed, or held by Hi-Rez in the United States and in

other countries, including, without limitation, countries both in and outside the European Union,

and used for the purposes set out in this Policy. You hereby consent to such use, storage and transfer

of your Personal Information.

8. RETENTION

Hi-Rez retains your Personal Information: (a) for so long as your account is active or as needed to

provide you with Services or to fulfill our contractual obligations; (b) as necessary to comply with

our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements; and (c) for so long as is

necessary for the purposes for which we collected such Personal Information.

9. SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will only collect and use Personal Information in accordance with this Policy to the extent

deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will use reasonable

safeguards to preserve the security, integrity, accuracy, and privacy of the information you have

provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer

any Personal Information will provide commercially reasonable protection of that information. We

cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Hi-Rez, and

you do so at your own risk. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information

may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical,

managerial, or other safeguards.

If Hi-Rez learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so

that you can take appropriate protective steps. Hi-Rez may post a notice on its Site if a security

breach occurs.

10. NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Shine the Light: Under California law, California residents who have an established business

relationship with Hi-Rez or its Affiliates may choose to opt out of Hi-Rez’s disclosure of Personal

Information about them to third parties for direct marketing purposes. As detailed in this Policy,

our policy is not to disclose Personal Information collected online to a third party for direct

marketing purposes without your approval. If you choose to opt-out at any time after granting

approval, contact our support desk at <http://www.hirezstudios.com/submit-support-ticket/\> or

email PrivacyRequests@hirezstudios.com or write to: Account Management, Hi-Rez Studios,

Inc., 3750 Brookside Parkway, Suite 200 Alpharetta, Georgia 30022.

Privacy Rights: California residents have certain rights under the California Consumer Privacy

Act (“CCPA”). Please see below for our CCPA Privacy Notice:

We have collected the following categories (as defined by the CCPA) of Personal Information

regarding California residents within the last 12 months from the sources listed below:

CATEGORY OF PERSONAL

INFORMATION COLLECTED SOURCES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Identifiers, such as your name, address, phone

number, email address, date of birth or other

similar identifiers.

You, our service providers and agents who

perform services on our behalf (“Vendors”), and

Social Networks.

Protected Classification Characteristics, such

as age and gender. You and Social Networks.

Commercial Information, such as shopping

and purchase history. You and your browser or device.

Internet/Network Information, such as device

information, logs and analytics data. Your browser or device.

Geolocation Data, such as precise location

information from your device or generated

based on IP address.

Your browser or device.

Sensory Information, such as audio recordings

of phone calls with us, where permitted by law. You.

Inferences from Personal Information

Collected, such as your preferences and your

likelihood of interest in certain of our games.

You, your browser or device, and Vendors.

As described in the “How We Share Your Information” section above, we share Personal

Information with third parties for business purposes such as:

• Audits and reporting relating to particular transactions and interactions, including online

interactions, you may have with us or others on our behalf;

• Detecting and protecting against security incidents, and malicious, deceptive, fraudulent

or illegal activity, and prosecuting the same;

• Debugging to identify and repair errors in our systems;

• Short-term, transient use including contextual customization of ads;

• Providing services on our behalf or on behalf of another, including maintaining or

servicing accounts, providing customer service, fulfilling transactions, verifying identity

information, processing payments, and other services;

• Conducting internal research to develop and demonstrate technology;

• Conducting activity to verify, enhance, and maintain the quality or safety of services or

devices which we may own, control, or provide; and

• Other business purposes described in the “Use or Sharing of Personal Information”

Section.

If you are a California resident, you have certain rights related to your Personal Information,

including:

• The right to request that we disclose to you:

o the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected;

o the categories of Personal Information we have collected about you;

o the categories of sources from which the Personal Information is collected;

o our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling Personal

Information;

o the categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information; and

o a list of the categories of Personal Information, such as name, address, e–mail

address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that we have disclosed

to third parties (including independent affiliates that are separate legal entities)

during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct

marketing purposes.

• The right to request that we delete the Personal Information we hold about you, unless the

Personal Information is necessary for the us or our service providers to:

o complete a transaction for which the Personal Information was collected, provide

a good or service requested by the individual or otherwise perform a contract

between us and the consumer;

o detect security incidents;

o protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent or illegal activity (or prosecute

those responsible);

o debug to identify and repair functionality errors;

o exercise or ensure the right of another to exercise free speech or another legal

right;

o comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act, which

compels the production of or access to electronic communication information or

electronic device information with a search warrant;

o engage in research in the public interest (if the consumer has provided informed

consent);

o to enable solely internal uses aligned with the consumer's expectations given their

relationship with us;

o comply with a legal obligation;

o otherwise use the information internally in a lawful manner compatible with the

context in which the consumer provided it.

• The right to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information. We do not sell and, within

the last 12 months, we have not sold Personal Information. However, we may use

advertising and tracking technology, which may be considered a sale under the CCPA.

For more information, please review our Hi-Rez Studios Cookie Policy, available at

<https://www.hirezstudios.com/legal/\>.

You may request to exercise these rights by contacting us at the addresses listed in the

“Communications” section below.

We may limit our response to your rights request as permitted under the CCPA. The right to

disclosure and right to deletion are not absolute and are subject to certain exceptions. For

instance, we cannot disclose specific pieces of Personal Information if the disclosure would

create a substantial, articulable, and unreasonable risk to the security of the Personal Information,

your account with us or the security of the business’s systems of networks.

As required under the CCPA, please note that we will take steps to verify your identity before

granting you access to information or acting on your request to exercise your rights. We cannot

effectuate your request if we are unable to verify your identity or authority to make the request

and confirm that the personal information relates to you. We may require you to provide your

email address to verify your identity in response to exercising requests of the above type. You

will, therefore, need access to your email account to receive our communications necessary to

process your request. Please make sure to check your spam inbox to ensure these important

communications are not missed. We will not use any Personal Information provided to us for

verification purposes for any reason other than to verify your identity.

You may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. You may make such a

designation by providing the agent with written permission to act on your behalf. We will require

the agent to provide proof of that written permission. As permitted by law, we may require you

to verify your own identity in response to a request, even if you choose to use an agent.

We endeavor to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt. If we

require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in

writing.

California Do Not Track: California Business \& Professions Code Section 22575(b) (as amended

effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how we

respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings. However, we do not currently take actions to

respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been

developed.

11. NOTICE TO RESIDENTS OF THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA AND

SWITZERLAND

This section only applies to individuals using or accessing our Service while located in the

European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland (collectively, the “Designated

Countries”) at the time of data collection. We may ask you to identify which country you are

located in when you use or access some of the Services, or we may rely on your IP address to

identify which country you are located in. When we rely on your IP address, we cannot apply the

terms of this section to any individual that masks or otherwise hides their location information

from us so as not to appear located in the Designated Countries. If any terms in this section conflict

with other terms contained in this Policy, the terms in this section shall apply to individuals in the

Designated Countries.

(a) Our Relationship to You.

We are a data controller with regard to any Personal Information collected from individuals

accessing or using its Services. A “data controller” is an entity that determines the purposes for

which and the manner in which any Personal Information is processed.

We use your Personal Information under certain legal bases permitted under the law, including:

• With your consent

• To satisfy legal obligations

• If we need to, to fulfill a contract with you, or to enter into a contract with you

• In the public interest

• In your vital interests

• Based on our legitimate interests

(b) Marketing

If you are located in the Designated Countries, we will only contact you by electronic means

(including email or SMS) for direct marketing purposes based on your consent. If you do not want

us to use your Personal Information in this way, please click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of

any of our email messages to you or contact us at PrivacyRequests@hirezstudios.com. You can

object to direct marketing at any time and free of charge.

(c) Individual Rights

We provide you with the rights described below when you use our Services. We may limit your

individual rights requests: (a) where denial of access is required or authorized by law; (b) when

granting access would have a negative impact on other’s privacy; (c) to protect our rights and

properties; or (d) where the request is frivolous or unrealistic. If you would like to exercise your

rights under applicable law, please contact us at PrivacyRequests@hirezstudios.com.

• You can request access or deletion of your Personal Information.

• You can correct or update your Personal Information, object to processing or your Personal

Information, ask us to restrict processing of your Personal Information or request

portability of your Personal Information.

• If we collected and processed your Personal Information with your consent, then you can

withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the

lawfulness of the processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect

processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing

grounds other than consent.

• You have the right to complain to your local data protection authority about our collection

and use of your Personal Information.

12. COMMUNICATIONS

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding our Policy or use of your

information, please contact our legal department at legal@hirezstudios.com.

Hi-Rez Studios

Attn: Legal Department

Email: legal@hirezstudios.com.

Or at:

Legal Department

Hi-Rez Studios, Inc.,

3750 Brookside Parkway, Suite 200

Alpharetta, Georgia 30022
